Guide to the Stella Sullivan artist papers, 1940-2016 MS 855
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Stella Sullivan artist papers
1940-2016
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Sullivan, Stella
MS 855
17 Linear Feet
Stella Sullivan was a Houston based artist and teacher, of the Midcentury Modernist genre. She worked with formats such as silkscreen prints, fabric art, watercolors, and more. Materials in this collection reflect the artist and teaching career of Stella Sullivan, including examples of her work, class notes, correspondence, and more.
Biographical / Historical
Stella Sullivan was a Houston based artist and teacher, of the Midcentury Modernist genre. She worked with formats such as silkscreen prints, fabric art, watercolors, and more. She died in 2018 at the age of 93.
Scope and Contents
Materials in this collection reflect the artist and teaching career of Stella Sullivan, including examples of her work, class notes, correspondence, and more.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request access by contacting woodson@rice.edu or calling 713-348-2586 and allow 24 hours retrieval time.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated in 2018 by the estate of Stella Sullivan, in collaboration with Foltz Gallery, Houston.
Index Terms
Subjects
Arts -- Texas; Artists -- Texas; Art
Document Types
letters (correspondence); prints (visual works); memorabilia; notes; obituaries; photographs; fabric art (visual works)
- Series I: Biographical
  - Biographical (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Newsclips (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rice Institute classwork (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art thesis, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Honors (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Telephone directories (Box 1, Envelope 7)
  - Birthday books (Box 1, Envelope 8)
  - Travel diaries-Rome, 1996 (Box 1, Envelope 9-10)
  - Sub-series A: Daybooks
    - 1955, 1956, 1957 (Box 1, Envelope 11)
    - 1958, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1960, 1961 (Box 1, Envelope 13)
    - 1962, 1963, 1964 (Box 1, Envelope 14)
    - 1964, 1965 (Box 1, Envelope 15)
    - 1966, 1967, 1968 (Box 1, Envelope 16)
    - 1970, 1971 (Box 1, Envelope 17)
    - 1972, 1973 (Box 2, Envelope 1)
    - 1974, 1975 (Box 2, Envelope 2)
    - 1976, 1977 (Box 2, Envelope 3)
    - 1978 (Box 2, Envelope 4)
    - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 1980, 1981 (Box 2, Envelope 6)
    - 1982, 1983 (Box 2, Envelope 7)
    - 1984, 1985 (Box 2, Envelope 8)
    - 1986, 1987 (Box 2, Envelope 9)
    - 1988, 1989 (Box 2, Envelope 10)
    - 1990, 1991, 1992 (Box 2, Envelope 11)
    - 1995, 1996, 1997 (Box 2, Envelope 12)
    - 1998, 1999 (Box 2, Envelope 13)
    - 2000, 2001, 2002 (Box 2, Envelope 14)
    - 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006 (Box 2, Envelope 15)
    - 2007, 2008, 2009 (Box 2, Envelope 16)
    - 2010, 2011 (Box 3, Envelope 1)
    - 2012, 2013 (Box 3, Envelope 2)
    - 2014, 2015 (Box 3, Envelope 3)
    - 2016, 2017, 2018 (Box 3, Envelope 4)
- Series II: Studio and classes
  - Stella Sullivan School of Art and Studio (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Studio open house and pricing, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Guest book, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Classes, general (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Classes, Post Oak Family Center YMCA, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Classes at studio (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tuition (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Class record, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Design 131, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Painting, ca. 1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Summer Camp, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - St. Catherine's Montessori, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Silkscreening (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Series III: Inventories, consignments, pricing
  - Portfolio (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Inventories, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Loans (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series A: Consignments
    - Inventories and consignments, ca. 2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - David Dike consignments (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Sally King consignments (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sally Gensheimer consignments (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Contracts (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sub-series B: Pricing
    - General (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Price estimates, printing (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
    - Price estimates, sewing (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Price estimates, illustrations (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Pricing worksheets, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Account Books (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
- Series IV: Gallery Showings
  - Biblical Arts Center Showing (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - David Dike Gallery (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - David Dike Gallery Showing (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kate Frost Showing (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Leslie Nuth Gallery Showing (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Modern Madonnas" Exhibit (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Modern Madonnas" Exhibit Guestbook (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Modern Madonnas" Exhibit Labeling (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Mulvey Gallery (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Pioneering Women..." Show (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Plain Folk Gallery Showings (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Reaves Gallery (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Reaves Gallery (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Surroundings Gallery Showing, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Surroundings Gallery (Box 4, Envelope 18)
  - "This Was Contemporary Art..." Exhibition (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ursuline Academy Gallery, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Various Exhibits, 1972, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Various Gallery Showings (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series A: Gallery Showings and Exhibitions by Others
    - David Adickes (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Art League of Houston (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Art + Frame, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Margarete Baum (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Bering + James Gallery (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Caseta (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Bill Condon (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Lee B. Davis (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Feldman Collection (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Frank Freed (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Handmakers (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Dorothy Hood (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Inter-American Craft Alliance (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Leila McConnell / Henry Gadbois (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Leila McConnell / Stella Sullivan (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - MFAH Archives / Sally Reynolds Project (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Charles Pebworth (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Charles Schorre (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - State Fair of Texas (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Richard Stout (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Summer-White Studios (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - James Surls (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Various Gallery Shows (Not Sullivan) (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Work by Others (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Open Houses (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Series V: Studio Materials and Artwork
  - Sub-Series A: Art Photos and Notes
    - "California Mountains" painting, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Church Works / Religious (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Holy Symbols (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - House Portraits (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Madonna Painting / Sally King Notes (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Painting Negatives (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Painting Slides (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Painting Slides (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Performing Arts Magazine (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Too Dark" Painting Photos and Slides (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Works (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series B: Studio (Letter-sized)
    - Design Notes (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Group a: Cards
      - Angels (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Design (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Christmas Design (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Examples (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - "Happy Happy Christmas" (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Images (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - "Joyous Noel" (Black and White) (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - "Joyous Noel" (Colourized) (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Madonna (Margaret Baum) (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Sub-Group b: Small Drawings
      - Drawings (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Bookplates (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Christmas Party - Tx A&M, Services, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Coat-of Arms, Betty Feehan (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Family Crests, Bouillane, Jobe (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Fashion (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Madonnas (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Fabric Samples (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Fabric Samples (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Ornaments: Angel (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Sub-Group c: Patterns
      - Angel (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Christmas Tree (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Measurements (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Rag Doll (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Printing Samples (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Supply Catalogs (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Watercolors (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Woodcuts (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series C: Studio (Legal-sized)
    - Sub-Group d: Designs
      - Fabric (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Magnificat House (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Paintings (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Performing Arts Magazines (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Rice University (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Sub-Group e: Drawings
      - Christmas (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Ornaments (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Design / Production (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Holy Rosary Church (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Houses (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Nameplates (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Portraits (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Saint Francis, Santa Fe, New Mexico (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Sketches (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Surroundings Gallery (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Wall Hangings - Episcopal Church of the Epiphany (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Fiber Artists of Houston (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Intercontinental Layout & Fabric Swatches (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Sub-Group f: Notebooks
      - English 100 notes, sketches (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Figures, Still Life (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Munsell Students Charts (color notation, hue comparison) (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Portraits, Figures, Still Life (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Religious Building Sketches (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Sketches - Figures, Swans & Ducks, St. Mary's Seminary (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Sketches & Watercolors - Protraits, buildings, birds (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Still Life practice w/ skull, lantern, & corn (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Studio Management Details (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Painting Detail Card Catalogue Cards (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Patterned Bags (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Series VIII: Realia and Memorabilia
  - Houston Yacht Club Emblem (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Article, Clippings (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series D: Programs
    - Cranbook Programs (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Julia Ideson Library Programs (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Rice Historical Society Programs and Invitations (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fiber Artists of Houston Programs (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "The Incomparable Sonja Henie" Programs (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Programs (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - School Notes (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series E: Travel
    - France, March, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Guides (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Papers (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Postcards, Pictures, Maps (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fabric crafts, printed tapestry (Box 8, Item 1-4)
  - 5 clay cups, 1 clay bowl (Box 8, Item 5-10)
  - 1 clay mission replica (Box 8, Item 11)
  - 1 Small woven basket (Box 8, Item 12)
  - 2 "a Se Ma handprint" cloth reels, plus paper labels (Box 9, Item 1-4)
  - Guys and Dolls calendar (Box 9, Item 5)
  - Stella Sullivan project binder completed by Margaret Sone (Box 9, Item 6)
  - Clay and wire trees art project (Box 9, Item 7)
  - Ceramic firing racks (Box 9, Item 8)
- Series VII: Correspondence and Obituaries
  - Correspondent List (Alphabetical) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Acuna (Da Cunha), Julio, 1954-2010 (Box 10, Folder 2-4)
  - Alexander, Robert, 1952-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Anderson, Evelyn, 1994-1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Attwell, Kirby, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - A Obituaries (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Balthauser, Barbara, 1953-1962 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Barnstone, Gertrude Levy, 1958-1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Barnum, Bette & Chuck, 1951-1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Barran, Clem, 1971-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Baum, Margarete, 1954-1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Beck, Audrey Jones Obituary (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Beck, Rudy, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Beckstead, George (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Behrs, The (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Berry, Bette and Marvin, 1967-1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Bert Rays, The (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Bessels, Jennette (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Best, Betty Jo Lackey, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Billfaldt, Jeanne, 1956-1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Boynton, Jack (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Bradbury, RM and Monica, 1955-1963 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Brennan, John Kent (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Burdisso, Jackie (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Bush, George W. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Bouliane, Mary Herd, 1939-1988 (Box 10, Folder 28-31)
  - B Obituaries (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Carling, Ingrid (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Carter, Jimmy (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Chamberlain, Jeanne E., 1989-1995 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Clok, Cousee (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Coleman, Pete (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Condon, Bill, 1943-1960 (Box 10, Folder 38-40, Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Connaly, 1951-1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Crandell, N. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - C Obituaries (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Didion, Ginger and Warren (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dieger, Sceter (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dolejska, Frank (also Shirley Nelson), 1952-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dubois, Mary and Margarete Baum (Box 11, Folder 8-15)
  - Duncan, Samuel (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Dvorak, Helen (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - D Obituaries (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Ely, William Stephen (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - E Obituaries (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Feehan, Harvey and Betty Malone (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Feehan, Thomas, and Virginia Arnold (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Flax, Phyllis (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - F Obituaries (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Gadbois, Henri (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Gale, Richard (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Geeslin, Gaddis and Gene (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Giesburg, Jean and Robert (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Giuliani, John (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Gracida, Henry (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Gragg, Annette and Hugh (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Guerrasio, Cathy (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - G Obituaries (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Haas, Greg (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Harle, Mary Lane, 1969-2000 (Box 11, Folder 35, Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Hawkins, Robert and Susan (Surroundings) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Hennessy, Joe (and Sister Eileen) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Hermon, Frances Ann (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Hickok, Cindy (Fabric Artists) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Hoey, William (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Hood, Dorothy (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - H Obituaries (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Invitations (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Jawlee, James Francis (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Jenkins, Rudy (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Ann and Arthur, 1953-2008 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - J Obituaries (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Keeper, David M. (Rose Keeper), 1995-2010 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Kendall, Sherman and Frank (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - King, F. B. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Kleiman, Alan (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Kopecky, Roy and Maggie (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Kora, Maikiko (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - K Obituary (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Laird, Ruth (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lang With Jr., John, 1944-2008 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lansdon, Gay (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lawrence, Clifford (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Layden, Patricia S., 1995 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Lea, Stanley, 1984-2014 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Liberato, Anthony F. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Lowe, Harry, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Lucy, Sr. Mary (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Lusk, Ursula Guseman (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Lytteton, Donald and Marian, 1971-1993 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - L Obituaries (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Maas, Elaine (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Mayo, Edward B "Bink" (and Bill Lassiter), 1943-2004 (Box 12, Folder 34-35)
  - McConnell, Leila and Henri Gadbois, 1950-2000 (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
  - Mears, Herb (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Medlin, Faith (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Monohan, Jimmie, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Moore, Lavoy and Ann (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Morrison, Betty and Boley Francis O'Bannon (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Muth, Leslie (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - M Obituaries (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Newton, Alsey and Kitty, 1987-2015 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Nunn, A. S. (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - N Obituaries (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Olskewsky, Freda (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - O'Malley, Kathleen (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Orman, Helen (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ory, Norma Ritt (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Owen, Jane Blaffer (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - O Obituaries (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Parrott, Alice Kagawa (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pebworth, Charles "Chuck" (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Perkins, John Alanson (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Peterson, Lysle and Sarah (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Peterson, Olga (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Putzel, Marcie (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - P Obituaries (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ray, Jack and Betty (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Ridgeway, Anne, 1946-1991 (2003) (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
  - Roche, Martha Alexander (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Romero, Cathy (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Rossi, Yolanda (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - R Obituaries (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Salazar, Salvator (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Schorre, Charles (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Seriff, Kay (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Kenneth (Sister Opal and Pete Summers) (Box 13, Folder 22-26)
  - Snow, J. L. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Stapleton, Connie (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Stewart, Noel, 1954, 1970-1975 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Stout, Richard (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Stuart, Lorraine A. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Sullivan, Mary Jane (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - S Obituaries (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Tapley, Charles and Charlotte (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Temple, Latane (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Tibbits, Randy (Rick Bebermeyer) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Tusa, Trish (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - T Obituary (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Uhler, Miss (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Umlauf, Charles J. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Unidentified Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Unsel, Annie L., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - U Obituary (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Voorheis, Carol (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Walton, Conrad G., 2008 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Ward, Marsha Lynn (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Waycott, Betty (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Williams, Ann Tuck (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Wray, Dick (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - W Obituaries (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Zoffman, Irene (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - X-Y-Z Obituaries (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Series IX: Oversize
  - Stella Sullivan, Self Portrait, 1949. oil on canvas, 24 x 18 inches (Box 14, Item 1)
  - Woodcut blocks (2) (Box 15, Item 1)
  - Stella Sullivan, Me in '63, oil on canvas, 24 x 18 inches (Box 15, Item 2)
  - Stella Sullivan, Bird's Eyes, oil on canvas, 12 x 16 inches (Box 16, Item 1)
  - Stella Sullivan, Squirrels in Flame, oil on canvas, 12 x 16 inches (Box 16, Item 2)
  - Stella Sullivan, October at Silver Dollar City, oil on canvas, 12 x 16 inches (Box 16, Item 3)
  - Stella Sullivan, Me in '54, oil on canvas, 24 x 18 (Box 16, Item 4)
  - Stella Sullivan, Untitled, oil on canvas, 12 x 16 inches, 2008-10 (Box 17, Item 1)
  - Stella Sullivan, Self Portrait, 1961, oil on canvas, 16 x 12 inches (Box 17, Item 2)
  - "Sit-down with Stella Sullivan" matted newspaper article (Box 17, Item 3)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art Master's Degree (Box 17, Item 4)
  - Sub-group A: People
    - Sketches (Map-drawer 99, Folder 1, Item 1-118)
    - Portraits (Map-drawer 99, Folder 1, Item 119-179)
    - Stylistic (Map-drawer 99, Folder 2, Item 1-22)
    - Religious (Map-drawer 99, Folder 2, Item 23-34)
    - Painted (Map-drawer 99, Folder 2, Item 35-139)
  - Sub-group B: Drawing Aids / Drafts (Map-drawer 99, Folder 3, Item 1-226)
  - Sub-group C: Still Life (Map-drawer 100, Folder 1, Item 1-33)
  - Sub-group D: Abstract (Map-drawer 100, Folder 1, Item 34-190)
  - Sub-group E: Mixed Materials
    - General (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 1-41)
    - Abstract Patterns (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 42-43)
    - Architectural (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 44-45)
    - Invitations, Workshop Announcements (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 46-54)
    - Oversize Written Pieces (Map-drawer 100, Item 55-69)
    - Christmas Cards (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 70-75)
    - Official Proclamations (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 76)
    - Rice Seal (Map-drawer 100, Folder 2, Item 77-81)
  - Sub-group F: Landscapes / Buildings (Map-drawer 101, Folder 1, Item 1-103)
  - Sub-group G: Matted Art (Map-drawer 101, Folder 2-3, Item 1-23 / 1-8)
- Series X: Newsclippings and photographs
  - Newspapers: Acquaintances and correspondents (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers: Art (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers: Art institutions (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers: Local news and society pages (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: Stella Sullivan (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Photograph of Stella Sullivan and photo of drawing of Katie Palmer (Box 18, Folder 6)